foreign
it's an absolute pleasure to have you
here thank you the pleasure is all mine
I would like to ask you
how do you balance the need for
innovation
and staying ahead in the market trends
while consistently maintaining in brand
image that insults that just in your
consumer in Target Market
great question so I'm sure you know the
tagline of ICICI Lombard is
so if we have to meet that and keep our
promises that's the focus that's the end
State objective that we have so we
ensure that whatever promises we make we
complete it that is our first objective
how do we do it we ride on four key
principles at ICICI Lombard we call
these Principle as vishwas principles
the principles of trust with our
customer so first principle is we are
fast and Nimble to respond to the
customer needs we do not give the
customer what we have in our bouquet we
go the extra mile talk to our customers
speak to them understand from them and
we do it in various ways so the way we
do it is we reach out to our customers
through customer service we make out
calls we conduct customer workshops we
do Road shows at societies also large
societies and we connect with our
customers personally and then once we
have understood their needs right from
them we Deliver Us for their ask so
that's one key difference but we do it
in a fast and Nimble way we take charge
we take ownership which is the next
principle that we follow so whatever we
do we ensure that if we've taken
ownership we deliver to the expectations
fulfill our promises going back to the
nibhayawada thing then we ensure we work
with the customer which I demonstrated
while talking to you and saying that we
talked to the customer walk together
with the customer to understand what he
or she requires and finally all these
successes that we achieve are celebrated
with the customer so we ensure that our
success that we achieve for example we
succeeded in delivering about one lakh
transactions on Riya in um a month which
is equivalent to our call center traffic
so we celebrated that success by sending
tokens of Thanksgiving to our customers
thank you notes Etc and we celebrated
the success with them for accepting Riya
wholeheartedly as their human oftar
customer communication mascot all right
um I would like you to talk a little bit
about your experience at most trusted
bfsi Brands 2023 by team Marksman and
Marksman daily so this is the second
edition of The bfsi
Summit however I've participated for the
first time and the best thing about this
is it is a short event
so I think the events the other events
that I attend they are complete one day
events rather I'd like to I prefer a
half day event where we can balance our
work as well as attend these Seminars
the Personnel the delegates also are
from leading Brands so I think that's
another thing I liked about it it's well
organized
thank you so much Messina thanks a lot
[Music]
thank you